(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-24T00:09:21.058073",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あ、あ、マイクテスト中。
Ah, ah, testing the mic.
聞こえてる？
Can you hear me?
オッケー。
Okay.
めっちゃ緊張する…
I'm so nervous...
深呼吸して、深呼吸。
Take deep breaths, deep breaths.
みんな、準備はいい？
Is everyone ready?
いつでもいけるよ。
Ready anytime.
よし、いこう！
Alright, let's go!
最高のライブにしよう！
Let's make this the best live show!
FLOW GLOW、いくぞー！
FLOW GLOW, let's go!
おー！
Yeah!
Yeah, This is FLOW GLOW from hololive DEV_IS.
お待たせしました！
Thanks for waiting!
FLOW GLOW 3Dお披露目ライブ！
FLOW GLOW's 3D debut live!
Make it! Break it! だ！
Make it! Break it!
楽しむ準備できてますかー！？
Are you ready to have some fun?!
搭載 V8エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第七感持ってる原人
A hominid with a seventh sense
ロックするこの世界と全人類
Locking up this world and all of humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
With these five, we're changing the game
唸る四輪 発射せよ
Launch the roaring four wheels!
皆さん 3Q サランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, saranghaeyo
操る2台のターンテーブル
Controlling two turntables
獲る1番 ここグランドゼロ
Taking first place, right here at ground zero
リスク超えて挑戦
Challenging beyond the risks
チャンスもセットだ 当然
A chance is set too, of course
登り上げる頂点
Climbing to the very top
座布団積んでく笑点
Stacking cushions like on Shoten
乗り込む FG ROADSTER
Climbing into the FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊 集合 能力者
Special forces assemble, ability users
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names into history
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
Leaving the trailing cars far behind
今高速でぶち抜いていく大気圏
Now breaking through the atmosphere at high speed
エンジンからジェットの炎揺れている怪気炎
Blowing a gale with jet flames swaying from the engine
眼下に広がる大地を越えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropic lines above the land below
バックミラーにBIG BLUEが写っている IBM
The big blue reflecting in the rearview mirror, IBM
打ち上げ台から飛んでく
Flying off the launchpad
うちら世代この燃料
Our generation is this fuel
朽ち果てないです銀河で
We won't decay even in the galaxy
寿司食べたい！
I want to eat sushi!
見えてるでっかいビジョン
I can see the big vision
燃えてるメンバー一同一兆度
All members are burning at a trillion degrees
ただいま現在進行形
Right now, currently in progress
超えてく世界規模
Going beyond global scale!
叶うはずだ Won't stop
It's bound to come true, won't stop
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are monsters
Aliens, turn it up
FG party hard
光る Tesla Roadster
The glowing Tesla Roadster
Heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Instincts are awakening
青い炎
The blue flame
BFF let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
From zero to space, without being bound
走る FG ROADSTER
Running, FG ROADSTER
唸る booster
Roaring booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
今 Chase me
Now chase me
フロミのみんな、楽しんでますかー！？
All the Flomies, are you having fun?!
FGちゃんたちも、もっともっとかます準備できてるー！？
Are the FG girls ready to kick it up even more?!
FG ROADSTERに続いてはこの曲！ 24K GOLD！
Following FG ROADSTER is this song! 24K GOLD!
我々は 翔る super girl
We are the flying super girls
金ピカの光 異次元
A golden light of another dimension
荒れ果てた世界 パトロール
Patrolling a ruined world
解き放て 踊れ
Unleash and dance!
私たち存在が純金
Our very existence is pure gold
いつでも万端な準備
Always prepared and ready to go
まるで無敵の宇宙人
Just like invincible aliens
春麗よりも俊敏
More agile than Chun-Li
サイドブレーキない突撃
A charge with no handbrake
ハイボルテージ毎度素敵
High voltage, always wonderful
催促です愛をくれ
I'm urging you, give me love
今乗っかってる波の上
Now riding high on the waves
変人凡人才人も
Weirdos, ordinary folks, and geniuses alike
みんなで遊ぼう最近どう？
Let's all have fun, how've you been lately?
流れてる flow like 合気道
Flowing like Aikido
戦闘力マイティー・ソー
With the combat power of Mighty Thor!
純度100%
100% purity
この爆発力マクラーレン
This explosive power of a McLaren
メッキに興味ないルパン三世
Lupin the Third, uninterested in cheap plating
この輝きならツタンカーメン
With this shine, it's Tutankhamun
髪風受けなびかせ
Letting the hair sway in the wind
Good, good, groove your body
Let it rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock on
心を突き動かせ
Stirring the heart
Good, groove your body
Good, good, groove your body
Level up, up, up, up, up, up
Look at me now
身に纏う flight suit は
The flight suit I wear is
24K GOLD
Ready to go
深い闇照らす輝き
A shine illuminating the deep darkness
24K GOLD
上にゆこう
Let's go to the top!
空飛んでいる wassup
Flying in the sky, wassup!
このケープが翼
This cape is our wings
滾っている power
Our power is boiling over
戦ってる super girl
Fighting like super girls
全身駆け巡る
Rushing through our bodies
満タンのガソリン
Full tank of gasoline
黄金の流星だ パッと見
Like a golden meteor at first glance
忍者みたい 半蔵服部
Like a ninja, Hattori Hanzo
強くて可愛くってかっこいい
Strong, cute, and cool
戦う 高鳴る
Fighting, heart racing
黄金の戦士 現る
The golden warriors appear!
渋谷 新宿 原宿
Shibuya, Shinjuku, Harajuku
風となり ちはやぶる
Becoming the wind, Chihayaburu
絶対撤退命令ない
Absolutely no retreat orders
アベンジャーズみたいな精鋭隊
An elite force like the Avengers
生成AIにはないオーラ
An aura that generative AI doesn't have
纏ってる輝く生命体
A glowing lifeform wrapped in it
追い風
Tailwind,
受け なびかせ
catch it and let it flutter!
G-G-G-Good body
Ready, lock, c-c-c-c'mon!
心を 突き動かせ
Stir up your heart!
G-G-G-Good body
Level up, p-p-p-p-pow!
抜け殻を身に纏う fly suit
Wearing a cast-off skin as a fly suit,
1, 2, 24K gold,
Ready to go!
深い闇照らす輝き
A radiance shining through the deep darkness,
解き放てよ
unleash it!
そう 次のステージへ FG Fighter!
Yes, to the next stage, FG Fighters!
FG! FG! FG! FG!
Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump! FG!
Flow Glow!
Flow Glow 3Dライブお披露目のご覧の皆さん！
To everyone watching the Flow Glow 3D Live Debut!
What's up?!
Here we are, Flow Glow!
先ほどは、FGロードスターと
Just now, we brought you a medley of "FG Roadster"
24K GOLDをメドレー形式でお届けしました！ありがとうございます！
and "24K GOLD"! Thank you so much!
いや、最初からど派手な登場すぎませんか？
I mean, wasn't that intro way too flashy from the start?
まあね！どうやったらみんなを「わぁっ！」て驚かせられるかって考えた結果だよね！
Well, yeah! It's the result of thinking how we could surprise everyone!
そうそう！そうなんだよね！一番ど派手なもんで行こうって言って！
Exactly! We said, "Let's go with the flashiest option possible!"
「一番ど派手なもんでいこう」って言って、モニターを突き破って来ました！
So we said that, and literally crashed right through the monitor!
突き破ったー！聞きいたことない！
We crashed through! Unheard of!
まあね、そんなはちゃめちゃすぎる私たちなんですけど、
Well, even though we're chaotic like that,
まずはね、自己紹介の方からさせて頂けたらなと思います！それでは私から！
we should probably start with our self-introductions! First up is me!
私の番！ Riona in the house!
It's my turn! Riona in the house!
Flow Glowのリーダー、伊咲りおなです！ぶらぶらー！
Flow Glow's leader, Riona Isaki here! Vroom vroom!
おー！
Ooh!
次はにこ！
Next up is Niko!
にこたんが... きたー！
Nikotan... is here!
ホロライブデバイス Flow Glowのお笑い担当、虎金にこです！にこたんだよ！イェーイ！
Hololive DEV_IS Flow Glow's comedy representative, Niko Kogane! Nikotan is in the house, yeah!
すーちゃん！
Su-chan!
そうやって来るのね！
So that's how you're doing it!
水分は、すーの充電！足りてる？
Hydration is Su's battery! Have you had enough?
ホロライブデバイス Flow Glowのエライセンター担当、水宮すーです！
Hololive DEV_IS Flow Glow's awesome center, Su Mizumi!
次はちは！
Next is Chiha!
はーい！エンジン全開レッツゴー！
Hi! Engine at full throttle, let's go!
Flow GlowのDJ兼運転手担当、輪堂千早です！今日も盛り上がってこうね！
Flow Glow's DJ and driver, Chihaya Rindo! Let's get fired up today!
次はビビ！
Next is Vivi!
はーい！いきますよ、せーの！うーービビ！
Yes! Here we go, ready, set... Vivi!
いや、こんなにキューティ、セクシー、ヘルシーでね、みんなもっとビビのこと好きになっちゃったなー、ほんまに！
I mean, I'm just so cute, sexy, and healthy, everyone must have fallen even more in love with Vivi, seriously!
おい、なんだよこのポーズ、マジで！
Hey, what is up with that pose, seriously?!
放送事故になるから！ばんばん！やだー！
That's a broadcasting hazard! Stop, stop! No way!
はい、ありがとね。ちははどう？
Okay, thank you. What about you, Chiha?
はい、ちははもちろん、この太もも！
Yes, for me, of course, it's my thighs!
みせてみせて！
Show us! Show us!
これでもう決まってんだから。ピンタイプだからね。
This is definitely the selling point. Because they're pinned.
すーちゃんはどうですか？
How about you, Su-chan?
はい、すーは、かっこいいかな、みたいな。やっぱイケてるかな、みたいな。いや、水宮ってかっこいい。
Well, for Su, I look cool, I guess? Like, totally stylish. I mean, Mizumi is just cool.
いや、そんなキャラじゃなかったよ！ばれちゃったな！
Wait, you weren't that kind of character! You've been exposed!
ち、ちこい... ちこい！
S-So cool... So cool!
え、にこたんは？
What about Nikotan?
にこたんは完全に虎。
Nikotan is completely a tiger.
え？さっきまで二足歩行じゃなかった？
Wait, weren't you bipedal until just now?
いやいや、ライブで踊るんだから四足にはできないでしょ！
No, no! We have to dance, so I can't go on all fours!
りおなはどうですか？
What about you, Riona?
そうですね、まあ、私も... 超セクシー、セクシーダンスをこの体でお披露目できるかなと思うと、すごく嬉しいです。
Yes, well, I... hope I can show off some super sexy dancing in this body, which makes me really happy.
素晴らしい！可愛い、楽しみです！ありがとう！
Wonderful! So cute, we're looking forward to it! Thank you!
そんな私たち5人でお届けする3Dライブ、そのハッシュタグについては、にこ、説明よろしくお願いします！
Niko, could you please explain the hashtag for our 3D live today?
はーい！今日の3Dライブのハッシュタグ、右上をご覧ください！ハッシュタグFG3Dライブです！
Okay! Please look at the top right for today's 3D live hashtag! It is #FG3Dライブ!
お気に入りのスクリーンショットに、このハッシュタグを加えてXでたくさんポストしてください！
Please share your favorite screenshots on X with this hashtag!
お願いします！トレンド1位目指すぞ！
Please do! Let's aim for trending #1!
トレンド1位目指すぞ！ライブを見てくれているみんな、ぜひコメントでFGちゃんたちに声援を送ってください！よろしくお願いします！
Let's aim for trending #1! Everyone watching, please cheer on the FG girls in the comments! Thank you!
はい、そしてライブの後半には、サプライズや重大発表もありますので、
And in the latter half of the concert, we have surprises and major announcements...
ぜひ最後まで楽しんでいただけると嬉しいです！ / お願いします！
so we hope you enjoy it to the very end! / We look forward to it!
ね、ちーちゃん、ちーちゃん。 / はいはい、なんですか？ / ハグ太郎置いてるのマズいかも。
Hey, Chihaya. / Yes, what is it? / Leaving Hug-taro parked there might be bad.
え、ダメなの？かっこいいよ？ / 東京、あの路上駐車はダメ。 / え、ダメ？
Wait, is it bad? It looks cool though! / Street parking in Tokyo is a no-go. / Really?
切られちゃうよ。 / 切られちゃう。 / 路上駐車、切られちゃう。
You'll get a ticket. / We'll get ticketed. / Street parking gets you a ticket.
ダメ！ダメ！撤去されちゃう！ / だから、あの、繋いでおくから、停めてきてもらって。
No, no! It'll get towed! / So, um, we'll keep the talk going while you go park it.
停めてきてくれる？ / もちろん、もちろん。 / 任せて、行ってきます！
Can you go park it? / Sure, of course! / Leave it to me, I'm on it!
じゃあ次の曲行こうか。 / 次の曲。 / 冗談はさておき。
Well then, should we go to the next song? / Next song. / Jokes aside...
1曲目から『FG Roadstar』と『24K GOLD』をメドレー形式でお送りしてきました！
We kicked off with a medley of "FG Roadstar" and "24K GOLD"!
なんと、その『FG Roadstar』のサビの振り付けは、すーちゃんがしてくれたんだよね！
And guess what? The choreography for the chorus of "FG Roadstar" was done by Suu-chan!
おおー！ / やっぱりちょっとカッコいい感じで。 / あ、ちーちゃん。
Wow! / I wanted to make it feel really cool. / Oh, Chihaya!
ちーちゃん、ありがとう。 / 黄色信号、守るよ。 / カッコいい感じで、こっからの振りを、作らせていただいたんですけど。
Thank you, Chihaya. / I'll obey the yellow light. / I got to choreograph this cool part starting from here.
いいよね。 / 好き。 / 皆さんもぜひいつか踊ってください！ / よろしくお願いします！
It's so good. / I love it. / Everyone, please try dancing it sometime! / Thank you!
びびたんは、メドレーやってみてどうだった？ / やっぱり、ずっとみんなに、初めて披露した時から、
Vivi-tan, how was doing the medley? / Well, ever since we first showed it...
リリースした時から、歌とダンスを一緒に見てほしいなと思ってたから、
actually, since we released it, I've really wanted everyone to see the song and dance together.
こうやってついに皆さんに観てもらうことができ、めっちゃ嬉しいです！カッコよかったやろー？
So I'm incredibly happy that we finally got to show you like this! Was it cool?
カッコよかった！ / めっちゃカッコよかったよ！
It was so cool! / You were super cool!
にこはどうやった？ / にこも楽しかった！色んな曲をくっつけて踊るのとかね。
How about you, Niko? / I had so much fun too! Dancing with all these different songs combined.
ちょっと今、頭真っ白で何喋ってるか全然わかんないや。
Honestly, my mind is completely blank right now, so I have no idea what I'm saying.
りおなはどうだった？ / そうだね、でもやっぱり、デビュー当時…と、と、と、と。
How about you, Riona? / Yeah, but as expected, since our debut... d-d-d-d...
緊張してる？ / 深呼吸、深呼吸！ / みんなで深呼吸しよう。
Are you nervous? / Take a deep breath! / Let's all take a deep breath.
深呼吸。 / 緊張してる。
Take a deep breath! / She's so nervous.
デビューの感想を言いたかったんだけど、うち等緊張してもうポロポロしちゃう。
I wanted to share my thoughts on our debut, but we're so nervous we're falling apart.
デビューしてから2曲出したオリジナル曲を、こうやって皆さんの前で動きありで披露することができて本当に素敵でしたし、
Being able to perform our two original songs with choreography in front of everyone was truly wonderful,
これからもFLOW GLOWのことをずっとよろしくお願いします！ / 泣くな、泣くな！ / 泣かないで！
and we hope you'll continue to support FLOW GLOW forever! / Don't cry! / Don't cry!
ありがとう。停めてきてくれたのもありがとうね。 / ファンの方の車が多すぎて、駐車場が全然空いてなくて。
Thank you. And thank you for parking the car. / There were so many fans' cars that the parking lot was completely full.
帰り気をつけようね、危ないから。
Let's be careful on the way home, it's dangerous.
そろそろみんなもライブ観たいかなと思うので、次の曲に参りたいと思います！
I think everyone wants to see more of the live performance, so we'd like to move on to the next song!
ついでにモニターも、なんか新しいものになりました！ / おおー！すごーい！
Also, the screen has changed to something new! / Whoa! Amazing!
じゃあね、まだまだライブは続くので、ますます盛り上がっていきましょう！
Alright, the live show is still going, so let's get even more hyped up!
それでは聴いてください、『LOAD』。
Now, please listen to "LOAD".
読み込みが完了しました。
Loading completed.
1 2 3 Jump
世界中に配信する ライブ ここはホロ
Live streaming all over the world, this is holo
80億の星の lights 照らす 心
Lighting up 8 billion stars' lights, illuminating my mind
通知が なる It's time to show my digital world
A notification rings, it's time to show my digital world
寝かせない 朝まで カーソル 合わせ 絵文字 の上
I won't let you sleep until morning, cursor on top of the emojis
スタジオにいる今日も 歌詞を書いてるノートに
Today too, I'm in the studio, writing lyrics in my notebook
変わる景色 相当 気づけばいたよ東京
The changing scenery is quite something, before I knew it, I was in Tokyo
夜空を見る首都高 乗る月に迎うボート
Looking at the night sky on the Shuto Expressway, a boat riding to the moon
みんなに見せる証拠 力になれることを
Showing the evidence to everyone, what can be a source of strength
ネガなマインド捨て 観てるだけじゃ意味ない
Casting away negative minds, just watching means nothing
夢じゃなくなった夢
A dream that is no longer just a dream
負けず嫌いで有名
Famous for being highly competitive
どこにもない終点
An endpoint that's nowhere to be found
君と見た星空の下 届きそうな手
Under the starry sky I saw with you, reaching out my hand
このデバイスがあれば どこへでも
With this device, I feel like I can go
行ける気がするよ 続く one way
anywhere, continuing on this one-way road
Stay with me by my side 遠いとこへ 2人で
Stay with me by my side, to the far side, just the two of us
この地球から virtual world
From this Earth to the virtual world
気にしない 今何時 何万キロ離れても
I don't care what time it is now, no matter how many thousands of miles apart
my team flow glow すぐ行動開始
my team flow glow, we start moving right away
チャット止まらない 24 調子がいい今日
Chat doesn't stop 24/7, I'm feeling great today
カメラにする はいチーズ 乗っ取ってる電波塔から放送する
Say "cheese" to the camera, broadcasting from the radio tower we took over
世界に配信
Streaming to the world
みてみな このスタイル 負ける気すらない
Look at this style, I don't even feel like losing
捨てる無駄な pride できるよこのくらい
Throwing away useless pride, I can do at least this much
みんなで今夜も party all night
Everyone together tonight, party all night
日々に上がる price やれるなら u better try
With prices rising day by day, if you can do it, you'd better try
世界中に配信する ライブ ここはホロ
Live streaming all over the world, this is holo
80億の星の lights 照らす 心
Lighting up 8 billion stars' lights, illuminating my mind
通知が なる It's time to show my digital world
A notification rings, it's time to show my digital world
寝かせない 朝まで カーソル 合わせ 絵文字 の上
I won't let you sleep until morning, cursor on top of the emojis
スタジオにいる今日も 歌詞を書いてるノートに
Today too, I'm in the studio, writing lyrics in my notebook
変わる景色速度 気づけばいたよ東京
Changing scenery and speed, before I knew it, I was in Tokyo.
夜空見下ろす灯光 乗る月に向かうボート
Lights looking down at the night sky, a boat heading towards the moon we ride.
みんなに見せるよ証拠 力になれることを
I'll show everyone the proof, that I can be a source of strength.
一生一度しか遊べない
You only get one life to play.
どう生きるか全部自分で決めたい
How to live, I want to decide it all myself.
好きなように生きてける世界で
In a world where we can live as we like...
広げていけるこの視界
we can expand our horizons.
Nyan nyan nyan nyan Bassを鳴らすステレオ
Meow meow meow meow, stereo pumping the bass.
音が降るライブ
Sound raining down at the live show.
フィルターの針を
Set the filter needle.
踊れるっしょ party girl
You can dance, right, party girl?
世界中に配信するライブ ここはホーム
Streaming this live show worldwide, this is home.
80億の星のライト 照らす今夜
The light of 8 billion stars illuminates tonight.
通知がないTime レジスタンスはオン
Time with no notifications, resistance is on.
お寝かせの悪魔で 覚悟合わせ文字の上
Putting the devil to sleep, matching our resolve over the letters.
100万マイル今日も 地図を書いてるノートに
Traveling a million miles today too, writing in the notebook where I draw the map.
変わる景色速度 気づけばいたよ東京
Changing scenery and speed, before I knew it, I was in Tokyo.
夜空見下ろす灯光 乗る月に向かうボート
Lights looking down at the night sky, a boat heading towards the moon we ride.
みんなに見せるよ証拠 力になれることを
I'll show everyone the proof, that I can be a source of strength.
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
I join the morning meeting in my pajamas.
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My routine clears my mind.
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
Mute screen from start to finish.
朝起きてえらい
Great for waking up in the morning.
傘持ってってえらい
Great for bringing an umbrella.
ネガティブあり得ない
Negatives are impossible.
自由に気分をリライト
Rewrite your mood freely.
背伸びしない 遠慮しない
Don't stretch, don't hold back.
ヤバいくらいゆるい my vibe
My vibe is so carefree.
描いてくカラーは自分次第
The colors I draw are my own.
オチない話をつづける鬼才
A genius who keeps talking with no punchline.
行き先決めないっていうフリースタイル
Freestyle: not deciding on where to go next.
指さされたけど気分はフライ
They pointed fingers, but I feel like flying.
眠たい 眠たい 眠らない tonight
Sleepy, sleepy, I won't sleep tonight.
無敵の状態
Invincible state.
態度デカいのは長所にしていいってお母さんが言ってた
My mom said that being big-headed can be a strength.
フィルター越しのsnapでピース
A peace sign with a snap through a filter.
本当の事は虹の彼方に
The truth is over the rainbow.
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Real and fake, just like a piece.
so who decides what's real?
not cool but good good enough
i'm still good good good enough
ちょっと loose but good good enough
A little loose but good, good enough
i'm still good good good enough
もっと fuel but good good enough
More fuel but good, good enough
i'm still good good good enough
not cool but good good enough
誤字脱字、日常茶飯事
Typos and omissions are commonplace.
また見逃し、寝過ごし
I overlooked it again, overslept,
それも生きてる証
that's proof that I'm alive.
未完成だからこそつくプレ値
It's unfinished, so it's worth a premium price.
磨けば必ず光る前提
It's guaranteed to shine if polished.
夢見てたころの自分はチャイルド
When I was dreaming, I was a child.
今日まで集めたフル装備でファイト
I'm fighting with all the gear I've collected so far.
ビビりだからこそ高めるマインド
Because I'm a coward, I raise my spirits.
褒めたい、褒めたい、たまに褒められたい
I want to praise, I want to praise, I want to be praised sometimes.
言葉じゃ足りない
Words aren't enough.
愛想がいいのは赤ちゃん的な時からっておばあちゃんも言ってた
My grandmother said that I've been friendly since I was a baby.
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
I join the morning meeting in my pajamas.
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My routine leaves me empty-headed.
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
Mute the screen from start to finish.
so who's in trouble, anyway?
not cool but good good enough
i'm still good good good enough
ちょっと loose but good good enough
A little loose, but good, good enough
i'm still good good good enough
もっと fuel but good good enough
More fuel, but good, good enough
i'm still good good good enough
not cool but good good enough
フィルター越しのsnapでピース
A peace sign with a snap through a filter.
本当の事は虹の彼方に
The truth is over the rainbow.
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Real and fake, just like a piece.
so who decides what's real?
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
I join the morning meeting in my pajamas.
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My routine clears my mind.
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
Mute screen from start to finish.
NEXT
忽哾りおな
Isaki Riona
輪堂千速
Rindo Chihaya
綺々羅々ヴィヴィ
Kikirara Vivi
虎金妃笑虎
Koganei Niko
水宮枢
Mizumiya Su
FLOW GLOW
SOLO PERFORMANCE
once upon a time
there was a little girl
君に よく 似てた
She really looked like you.
oh darling 君に 似てた
Oh darling, she was just like you.
彼女は まるで タイガーアイ
She was just like a tiger's eye.
無数の 欲 より 大事な
She had found herself a dream,
夢を 見つけ ては
more precious than any kind of greed...
掴んで しまった
and she made it hers.
ある 夜 雨 が 降ってた
One night, it was raining.
濡れた 瞳に ぼやけた
Dewy eyes saw a blurry light.
嘘の ように 美しい
It was beautiful like a lie...
ダリアが 微笑んでた
as a dahlia smiled at her.
i want the same one
それが 欲しい のと 吐き捨ててこう言った
"That's what I want," she spat out and said.
引き換え に 何が 欲しい?
What do you want in return?
奏でろ 賛美歌
Now go on and play that hymn.
無知 な メロディー は ハイ
A melody of ignorance is high.
たかが 心 なら 差し上げたいわ
If all you want is my heart, I'd love to give it away.
甘ったるい 願いね
What a sickly sweet wish.
そして 彼女 は just a ダリアのように
And then she was just like a dahlia.
no ダリア
No... dahlia.
あらためまして、咲季このはです！
Once again, I'm Saki Konoha!
名前、覚えて帰ってください！
Please remember my name before you leave!
乱心 内心 邁進 ego
Disturbed, inner mind, pushing forward, ego.
up & down always get into trouble
Up and down, always getting into trouble.
「 楽しい 」 「 正しい 」 「 嬉しい 」 でも
Even if it's fun, correct, or happy,
平常 me 、 sold out
my usual self is sold out.
あれ ナシ これ ナシ
None of this, none of that.
合わせる 段々 敵 なし
Adjusting step by step, there's no match.
己 の way ?
My own way?
また ゼロ へ get away
Getting away back to zero again.
wisper to my ears
Whisper to my ears,
oh give me some more details
手招き 脱 して 、 勝ち
Escaping the summons, I win.
no way slipping and breaking down
か ませ 急上昇
Make an impact, rapid rise!
はな て 絶好調 own way now
Release it, in top form, my own way now!
better show what i gotta gotta show !
Better show what I gotta, gotta show!
ima shake it , lets go . next !
I'm gonna shake it, let's go. Next!
変幻 理想 像
An ever-changing ideal image.
come again , 熱狂
Come again, wild enthusiasm.
hey show me what you got
Hey, show me what you've got.
i 'm breaking down pretty me
I'm breaking down, pretty me.
next side next side ...
Next side, next side...
楽しんだら upboomboom !
If you enjoy it, upboomboom!
trip in the dark ...
Trip in the dark...
such a funny thing for me to explain
it 's ok even if you don't understand
It's okay even if you don't understand.
l just wanna make you roll
I just wanna make you roll.
ルール は ない unchain
There are no rules, unchain.
頭 と 心 awake now
Head and heart, awake now.
アブラカタ blah blah blah 幻 なら
Abracadabra, blah blah blah. If it's an illusion...
無理 × 3 価値 なし 無視 ah just do it !
Impossible x3, worthless, ignore. Ah, just do it!
are you ready let 's play game ! !
Are you ready? Let's play the game!
万人 万事 愛して は 一 蓮 托生 三千 世界
Loving all people and all things, sharing one's fate in the vast world.
dancing 突進 童心 get up
Dancing, charging forward, with a childlike heart, get up!
全方位 call out
Calling out in all directions.
人生 も 来世 も
In this life and the next,
i wish days were longer than 24
曇り なく いたい の yeah
I want to stay without a single cloud, yeah.
i 'm feeling really mellow
I'm feeling really mellow,
oh i wanna feel more
たまに は わがまま に
Sometimes, being selfish is fine.
now hey , come in and turn it loud
Now hey, come in and turn it loud.
鳴らせ 鼓動 を
Make your heartbeat resonate.
醒ま せ 最高潮 own way now
Awaken the climax, my own way now!
better show what i gotta gotta show …
Better show what I gotta, gotta show...
gotta show what i wanna wanna show !
Gotta show what I wanna, wanna show!
ima shake it , lets go . next !
I'm gonna shake it, let's go. Next!
変幻 理想 像
An ever-changing ideal image.
come again , 熱狂
Come again, wild enthusiasm.
hey show me what you got
Hey, show me what you've got.
i 'm breaking down pretty me
I'm breaking down, pretty me.
next side next side ...
Next side, next side...
楽しんだら upboomboom !
If you enjoy it, upboomboom!
na na na yeah
na na na na na na na na
let 's make it loud !
Let's make it loud!
la - ta - ta - tat !
La-ta-ta-tat!
next side next side ...
Next side, next side...
楽しんだら upboomboom !
If you enjoy it, upboomboom!
一度はあの光を見たんだよ とってもキレイで
I saw that light once, and it was so beautiful.
でも今思えば汚かった あれはいわゆるBad Day Dreams
But thinking back now, it was dirty; they were bad daydreams.
光が眩しすぎて周りが見えず ただただ日々を
The light was so blinding that I couldn't see my surroundings,
棒に振ってたあの日 今だから笑えるよ
and just wasted those days away. Now, I can laugh about it.
一度はあの幕を開けたんだよ とっても重くて
I opened that curtain once, and it was so heavy.
プレッシャー、イヤ味それに勝つために ただ嫌なヤツで
To overcome the pressure and sarcasm, I acted like a jerk.
そして気が付くと真っ暗な部屋に一人ぼっちだった
And before I knew it, I was all alone in a pitch-black room.
終わった... もう戻れない... なんて... 歩くのも止めた...
"It's over... I can't go back..." I even stopped walking.
外は I'm not alone, I'm not alone
But I'm not alone, I'm not alone.
We're not, We're not, We're not alone
お金じゃ買えないもの手に入れて
I'll get my hands on things that money can't buy.
もう一度光浴びて そして今度は騙されぬように
Bathed in the light once more, and this time, not to be fooled,
僕らは今目指すよ 欲望に満ちた青年団
we're now aiming to be a group of youths filled with desire.
誰かが言った言葉 それすらその時は流して保存
Even the words that someone once said, I just let them slide back then.
今になって気付いたよ 欲望に負けた少年団
Only now have I realized we were a group of boys defeated by desire.
So, I know you know? You know I know?
We have, we have, we have grown
囚われないようにと上向いて歩く
Walking with my head held high so I won't be trapped.
もう一度光浴びて そして今度は騙されぬように
Bathed in the light once more, and this time, not to be fooled,
僕らは今目指すよ 欲望に満ちた青年団
we're now aiming to be a group of youths filled with desire.
誰かが言った言葉 それすらその時は流して保存
Even the words that someone once said, I just let them slide back then.
今になって気付いたよ 欲望に負けた少年団
Only now have I realized we were a group of boys defeated by desire.
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much!
あ、おはよ
Ah, morning!
朝起きて まず確認 今日もいい感じだね
Waking up in the morning, first I check. Looking good today, too!
1年365日 私のこと一番見てる人
365 days a year, the person who looks at me the most...
「好きです」と言えるのは 当たり前とかじゃない
Being able to say "I love you" isn't something to take for granted.
1日8万6千400秒 ずっと付き合ってくんだから
Because we'll be together for all 86,400 seconds of the day.
ママから聞いたことあるわ
I've heard this from my mom before:
見た人を好きになるんじゃなくて
You don't just fall in love with someone you see,
好きな人には似るものらしいです 本当で
apparently, you grow to resemble the one you love. It's true!
みんな思ったことあるわ保存
Everyone has thought about it before:
目を開けたら違う自分になって
What if I wake up as a different person?
いやいやもっと真剣に 変身
No, no, let's take this more seriously... Transform!
マスカラ塗るわ (うるうる)
I'll put on mascara (making my eyes watery)
口紅塗るわ (ぷるぷる)
And lipstick (making my lips plump)
あれ？可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
Oh? Maybe I've become a bit too cute?
もうさすがに盛りすぎちゃったかも
Geez, maybe I've overdone it with the makeup?
あなたの真似したんです
I did it to copy you,
だって超大好きなんだから
because I love you so, so much!
鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit,
可愛くなってもいいのかな？
is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay true to yourself.
それで
And so...
ヒミツ ヒミツ ヒミツの可愛い子ちゃんにはなれない
I can't be your secret, secret, secret cute girl.
そんなこと全部お見通しです だって逆に
I can see right through all of that! Because conversely,
ヒミツ ヒミツ ヒミツは私たちにはいらない
we don't need any secrets, secrets, secrets.
だけどあなたが秘密にしたいほど可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
But, I might have become so cute that you'll want to keep me a secret!
朝起きて ちょうど休み
Waking up in the morning, and it's a day off!
やりたいことありすぎ
There are too many things I want to do.
1日は24時間って言うけど ずっと起きてるわけでもない
They say a day has 24 hours, but it's not like I can stay awake the whole time.
帰ったらまた確認 当たり前とかじゃない
When I get home, I'll check again, it's not something to take for granted.
とにかく自分を大事にしましょう
Anyway, let's take good care of ourselves,
ずっと付き合ってくんだから
since we'll be together forever.
ママから聞いたことあるわ 10時から2時は寝るのがよくて
I've heard from my mom that sleeping between 10 PM and 2 AM is best,
6時以降は食べない方がいい いや、無理です！
and it's better not to eat after 6 PM. No way, that's impossible!
みんな思ったことあるわ
Everyone has thought about it:
寝てる間に変わらないのかな
"I wonder if I'll change while I'm asleep?"
いやいや、やっぱ真剣に変身したい！
No, no, I seriously want to transform!
マスカラ塗るわ (うるうる)
I'll put on mascara (making my eyes watery)
あれ？可愛くなりすぎちゃっていい？
Oh? Is it okay if I become too cute?
本当に盛りすぎちゃっていい？
Is it really okay if I overdo it?
あなたのこと好きです
I love you,
だって超前向きなんだから
because I'm super positive!
鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit,
可愛くなってもいいのかな？
is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay true to yourself.
もう大好き 大好き 大好きって 目の前の君に言っていいのかな？
I love you, love you, love you so much—is it okay to say that to you right in front of me?
自分で今魔法かけます
I'm casting a spell on myself now.
嘘でもかかったフリしてね
Even if it's a lie, pretend you fell for it, okay?
でも私もあなたも嘘がつけない
But neither you nor I can lie,
そういう奴だからさ
because we're just that kind of person.
マスカラ塗るわ (うるうる)
I'll put on mascara (making my eyes watery)
あれ？可愛くなりすぎちゃっていい？
Oh? Is it okay if I become too cute?
本当に盛りすぎちゃっていい？
Is it really okay if I overdo it?
あなたのこと好きです
I love you,
だって超前向きなんだから
because I'm super positive!
鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit,
可愛くなってもいいのかな？
is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay true to yourself.
あれ？可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
Oh? Maybe I've become a bit too cute?
もうさすがに盛りすぎちゃったかも
Geez, maybe I've overdone it with the makeup?
あなたの真似したんです
I did it to copy you,
だって超大好きなんだから
because I love you so, so much!
鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit,
可愛くなってもいいのかな？
is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって正直にいて
Always stay true to yourself.
それで ヒミツ ヒミツ ヒミツの可愛い子ちゃんにはなれない
And so, I can't be your secret, secret, secret cute girl.
そんなこと全部お見通しです だって逆に
I can see right through all of that! Because conversely,
ヒミツ ヒミツ ヒミツは私たちにはいらない
we don't need any secrets, secrets, secrets.
だけどあなたが秘密にしたいほど可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
But, I might have become so cute that you'll want to keep me a secret!
終わらない夜の途中
In the middle of an endless night,
灯りを忘れた空には
In the sky that has forgotten its light,
戻れない日の指切りを
A pinky promise of days we can't return to,
カシオペアの代わりに
In place of Cassiopeia,
灯りになった
It became a light.
だから物が落とす影を追っていたら
So, as I chased the shadows cast by objects,
真っ暗に紛れて混ざって
They blended and mixed into the pitch-black darkness,
見つけられないままで
Remaining lost and unfound.
いくつもの青を分けて
Parting through countless shades of blue,
繰り返す景色を泳ぐ
I swim through the repeating scenery.
心がまだ突っかかりながら
Though my heart is still catching on things,
その為だけに動いてる
It moves solely for that purpose.
これはきっと帰り道
This is surely the way home,
夢の向こうに続く道
A path leading beyond dreams.
綻びた歌をまとえば
If I wrap myself in a worn-out song,
何も怖くはない
I have nothing to fear.
命は理由に出会えた
My life has found its reason,
燃えて消える意味を知った
Knowing the meaning of burning away.
その東が今を照らした
That eastern dawn has illuminated the present,
青く青くとどこまでも
Blue, blue, endlessly.
明日が全てを失っても
Even if tomorrow loses everything.
あなたのことだけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing only of yourself,
ならば私は戦える
if so, I can fight.
たとえこの身が危険だとしても
Even if this body is in danger.
思い馳せなくなった虹を覚えてる空には
In the sky that remembers the rainbow I no longer think of,
くたびれた靴が響くよ
the sound of worn-out shoes echoes.
それでも歩いてると
Even so, as I keep walking,
掴もうとしてすり抜けた
the words that slipped away as I tried to grab them,
言葉忘れない手のひら
the palm that will never forget them.
指を蓋にして隠して
Hiding them by covering them with my fingers,
強さに変える魔法
a magic that turns them into strength.
ああ あとどれだけ息をしたら
Ah, how many more breaths must I take
これでよかったと思える
before I can think that this was for the best?
心がずっと砕けたから
Since my heart has been broken for so long,
欠片の全部で動いている
it moves with all of its fragments.
これはやっと帰る道
This is finally the way back home.
あの日と同じじゃなくていい
It doesn't have to be the same as that day.
ただもう一度だけ会いたい
I just want to meet you once more,
何も怖くない
nothing is scary anymore.
泣かないでと祈るのは
What I pray for, asking not to cry,
足跡の下の涙
are the tears beneath the footprints.
迷いをのけたつま先で
With toes that have cast aside doubt,
進め 進め 魂ごと
go forward, go forward with all your soul!
正しいかどうかということよりも
More than whether it is right or wrong,
あなたのいる世界が笑ってほしい
I want the world you are in to smile.
だから私は生きている
That's why I am alive.
時計の針にも奪えない力
A power that even the hands of a clock cannot steal.
独りになったから
Because I became alone,
宝物が落とす影まだ探してる
I'm still searching for the shadow cast by my treasure.
ああ もう一度だけ会いたい
Ah, I just want to meet you once more,
何も怖くない
nothing is scary anymore.
命は理由に出会えた
Life has found its reason.
燃えて消える意味を知った
I learned the meaning of burning and disappearing.
その陽が視界を照らした
That sun illuminated my sight,
青く 青く どこまでも
blue, blue, endlessly.
明日がすべてを失っても
Even if tomorrow loses everything,
繋げたことだけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing only of the connection we made.
だから私は生きている
That's why I am alive,
欠片の全部で
with all of its fragments.
泣かないでと祈るのは
What I pray for, asking not to cry,
足跡の下の涙
are the tears beneath the footprints.
迷いをのけたつま先で
With toes that have cast aside doubt,
進め 進め 魂ごと
go forward, go forward with all your soul!
間違いかどうかということよりも
More than whether it is a mistake or not,
あなたのいる世界が続いてほしい
I want the world you are in to continue.
ならば私は戦える
If so, I can fight.
たとえその時そばにいないとしても
Even if I'm not by your side at that time.
この地球上全てが俺の遊び場
This entire world is my playground.
半端な覚悟で汚すなよ坊や
Don't mess around half-heartedly, kid.
リアリスト気取りのビビリ屋
You act tough as a realist but you're just a coward.
話になんねぇ
Your talk is meaningless.
なんでそんなに自信があるんですか？
Why are you so confident?
手前で掴んだ結果だ当たり前じゃん
It's obvious from the results I've achieved.
ジャーナリスト気取りの皮肉屋
You act like a journalist but you're just sarcastic.
話す気になんねぇ
You have no intention of talking.
毒を喰らえ 栄養を喰らえ
Swallow the poison, consume the nutrients.
テメェの味出しで決まる持ち味を活かせ
Bring out the flavor determined by your unique taste.
One way or another way お前が一体どうしたいかだって?
One way or another way, it's about what you truly want.
さぁ おかわりはいかがですか?
So, would you like seconds?
夢を越えろ
Transcend the dreams.
そこから上を向けよ
Look up from there.
本物に飢えろ
Hunger for authenticity.
ここまで来いよ
Come this far.
Come at me
夢は超えろ
Surpass your dreams!
wow wow ここまで来いよ
Wow, wow, come on over here!
端も屁理屈 理屈が堪んない
On the edge, even excuses... I can't stand the logic.
安定も安心も手伝いにはなんない
Neither stability nor security will help you.
次にやる予定もテメェの好きにやりな
Do whatever you want with your next plans too.
離さないよベイビー
I won't let you go, baby.
もうちょい遊んで頂戴
Play with me a little longer.
馬鹿にしてるって とんでもない
You think I'm making fun of you? No way.
おーらいバイキング 食べ放題 ただ毒に当たってもどんまい
All right, buffet, all you can eat, even if you get poisoned, don't worry about it.
お味の程はいかがですか？
How does it taste?
夢は超えろ
Surpass your dreams!
そこから上を向けよ
And look up from there!
リアルに植えろ 植えろ
Plant it, plant it in reality!
wow wow ここまで来いよ
Wow, wow, come on over here!
噛み砕け 噛み砕け
Chew it up, chew it up!
夢は超えろ
Surpass your dreams!
wow wow ここまで来いよ
Wow, wow, come on over here!
待てない 待たない いくらあっても足りない
Can't wait, won't wait, no matter how much there is, it's not enough!
腹いっぱい 食べたい テメェをやってきさらい
I want to eat my fill, I'll take you away.
あの子のこと どの子のこと 誰もが欲しがるものを分け取るのが仕事
That girl, which girl? Our job is to divide and take what everyone wants.
味も 毒も 薬も 毒も 頂く高級なフルコース
Taste, poison, medicine, poison, a luxurious full-course meal to partake in.
通知とかはオフ
Notifications are off.
お行儀良く 上手 もっとシャープにショートボブ
Well-behaved and skillful, a sharper short bob.
ストップの時で凍ったトップオブザトップ
The top of the top, frozen at the moment of stop.
夢は超えろ そこから上を向けよ
Surpass your dreams, and look up from there.
リアルに植えろ 植えろ
Plant it, plant it in reality!
wow wow ここまで来いよ
Wow, wow, come on over here!
噛み砕け 噛み砕け
Chew it up, chew it up!
夢は超えろ
Surpass your dreams!
wow wow ここまで来いよ
Wow, wow, come on over here!
噛み砕け 噛み砕け
Chew it up, chew it up!
夢は超えろ
Surpass your dreams!
wow wow ここまで来いよ
Wow, wow, come on over here!
あれが世界なんて
To think that is the world...
誰の成れの果て
Whose ruined remains are they?
答えの欲しいもの一個ってこれだけ
The only thing I want an answer to is just this.
悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
There's no use worrying, is there?
あれは夢だったって思うことにしたって
Even if I decide to think of it as just a dream...
でも全然思えないんだけど
...I can't seem to think that way at all.
助けてよプロデューサー
Save me, Producer!
抗うだけ 若さに負け
Just resisting, losing to youth.
next, next, next, lucky, lucky, lucky
アーリーオ割り切れたらさ
If only I could cleanly divide it...
オーリーオ楽なのにとか
...it would be so much easier.
aah... もうヤダ！
Aah... I hate this already!
なんという新世界か
What kind of new world is this?
あなた以外は あなた以外はいらない
Anyone but you, I don't need anyone but you.
張らないでよバリア
Don't put up a barrier.
あるはずの何かあったならば happy jumpin' yeah!
If there was something that should be there, happy jumpin' yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしのこの手を
If your hand and my hand...
繋いだらもう二度と離さないわ
...are joined, I'll never let go again.
あなたのその手があたしのこの手を掴んだら...
If your hand grabs my hand...
以後お見知りおきを！my love
From now on, please remember me! My love.
ニコちゃんが来たー！
Niko-chan has arrived!
エンジン全開！レッツゴー！盛り上がっていくぞ！レッツゴー！
Engine at full throttle! Let's go! Let's get fired up! Let's go!
うるうるの充電、足りてる？足りてないよな！
後半戦も盛り上がっていくぞー！
Is your 'uruuru' charge full? It's not enough, is it!
Let's get fired up for the second half too!
みんなのこと、もっとメロメロにしちゃうぞ！
後半戦、せーの、うー、びび！
I'm going to make everyone fall even more head over heels!
Second half, ready, set, oo-bibi!
みんなに出会えて、とっても幸せです！
画面の向こうのみんな、声出せ！おらー！
I'm so happy to have met you all! Everyone on
the other side of the screen, make some noise! Come on!
新しい姿のFLOW GLOWで、新しい曲。
聴いてくれ、MAKE IT, BREAK IT.
A new song from FLOW GLOW in our new forms.
Please listen: MAKE IT, BREAK IT.
よし！
Alright!
Make it, break it / Break it, break it
Make it, break it / Rock on!
認め合えば相棒 君こそが相棒
メロつかせる才能 make it break it
If we acknowledge each other, we're partners; you are indeed my partner
A talent to make people fall head over heels, make it, break it
ハッタリかましてても 勘違いされても
Even if we're bluffing, even if we're misunderstood.
そのギャップと愛嬌あれば最強
ヘイターは仕事（へえ、そう）
With that contrast and charm, we're the strongest
Haters are just doing their job (oh, really?)
一蓮託生 退がらない 退屈に用はない
Sharing the same fate, we won't back down;
we have no use for boredom.
一線画すよ バチバチ 妥協ない しょうがない
Drawing a line, sparks flying, no compromise, can't be helped.
うち等がつるめばparty party party
When we hang out, it's a party, party, party!
Make a revolution...
髪揺らしながら
Swaying our hair...
置いてかない絶対
We'll never leave you behind!
付いてきて 5MCs
Follow us, 5MCs!
本気の Friday night
This serious Friday night!
Make it, break it!
Make a revolution 私を貫け
Make a revolution, stick to my way!
歌舞け 夢に恋 恋 恋 恋 恋
Dance wildly! Fall in love with dreams, come on!
No, play will never stop
No, the play will never stop!
真ん中 ぶち抜け ゆけ ゆけ Can get it now
Break straight through the center, go, go, can get it now!
You see, Make it, Break it
Make it, Break it
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You see, Make it, Break it
Make it, Break it
ほら どっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
騒々沸くプロローグ 行き先より行動
An exciting, bustling prologue, action over destination!
If you want to be my men よそ見とかは無しで
If you want to be my men, no looking away!
ほい もっと ほら もっと ほら 慌てちゃって
Hey, more! Look, more! Look, getting flustered!
ほい もっと ほら もっと ほら 本気になっちゃって
Hey, more! Look, more! Look, getting serious!
置いてかない絶対
We'll never leave you behind!
付いてきて 5MCs
Follow us, 5MCs!
本気の Friday night
This serious Friday night!
Make it, break it!
Brand new generation 感じるまま駆けれ
Brand new generation, run as you feel!
上がれ 華麗に今 踊れ 踊れ 踊れ
Rise up, beautifully now, dance, dance, dance!
Tight! つなぐNever land
Tight! Connecting Never Land.
さあ これ 抜け出して
Now, escape from this!
汗ありのまま
Sweat, just as it is!
You see, Make it, Break it
Make it, Break it
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You see, Make it, Break it
Make it, Break it
朝まで 眠らせない
Won't let you sleep until morning!
FG！ 行くぞ！
FG! Let's go!
Make a revolution 私を貫け
Make a revolution, stick to my way!
歌舞け 夢に恋 恋 恋 恋 恋
Dance wildly! Fall in love with dreams, come on!
No, play will never stop
No, the play will never stop!
真ん中 ぶち抜け ゆけ ゆけ Can get it now
Break straight through the center, go, go, can get it now!
You see, Make it, Break it
Make it, Break it
Bang! Bang! Bang!
You see, Make it, Break it
Make it, Break it
ほら どっちにするの？
Hey, which one will you choose?
いよいよ次が最後の曲です。
聴いてください、stay by my side
Finally, the next song is our last one.
Please listen to 'stay by my side'.
ずっと切らせない みんなとのファーストステージ
I'll never let this first stage with everyone end.
いつもより濃いメイク あれはフェイクフェイス
Thicker makeup than usual—that was a fake face.
見せてく張りぼて 期待と不安詰め込んで 歩き出したんだ せーので
Showing our facade, filled with expectations and anxiety, we started walking on three.
強がってた泡立つようなビビり でもみんなに気付かされた そのままでええやん
Acting tough with a bubbly fear, but everyone made me realize, it's fine just as I am.
勝てる当たり前じゃないこの日々 パチもんになっても一緒にいたいよバイビー
This daily life that isn't easy to win, even if we become cheap imitations, I want us to be together, bye-bee.
気付いたら騒がしい毎日 違う歩幅 どこに行くの？私たち
Before I knew it, every day was noisy, with different strides, where are we going?
迷う自分 みんながくれる刺激 馴れ合いじゃない これって素敵？
Losing myself, the stimulation everyone gives me, it's not just getting cozy, isn't this wonderful?
まだリーダーって胸張れなくとも 持てる何かあれば立てるだけの覚悟
Even if I can't proudly call myself a leader yet, if I have something to hold on to, I have the resolve to stand.
自分のため私歌って踊るステージ flow flow 刻む響き めくるめく日々
For myself, I sing and dance on this stage, flow flow, carving the rhythm, dizzying days.
stay by my side 夜中になってもまだ寝れない
stay by my side, even in the middle of the night, I still can't sleep.
イェイ あとどのくらい？辿り着くあの夢の世界
Yeah, how much longer? Reaching that dream world.
初めて会ったあの日 輪になって遊んだり
That day we met for the first time, playing in a circle...
ここまで歩いてきた未来 今でも覚えてる
The future we walked to get here, I still remember it even now.
stay by my side 街角で二人
stay by my side, two of us on the street corner.
by my side 考えてる一人
by my side, thinking all alone.
無駄にはならないからあの涙も
Because they won't go to waste, those tears too.
今ここ by my side 寄り添ってる隣
Right now here, by my side, snuggling next to me.
ずっと昔はぐれた炎
A flame that went astray long ago.
夜を必死に照らしたこと
Desperately lighting up the night...
集まる星はドットのよう それはあの日 これからも残る音
Gathered stars like dots, that day, the sound will remain from now on.
暗闇の中見えない青い愛
Blue love unseen in the darkness.
道標はあなたのサイド
The signpost is by your side.
光をこの手を離さないで
Don't let go of this hand with light.
空の始まりよりきらめいて
Sparkling more than the beginning of the sky.
最初一人の同じ夢追い
At first, chasing the same dream alone.
じゃない、もう一人じゃない
No, we are not alone anymore.
隅々浴びるプログローの宇宙
The universe of Prog-Glow, bathed in every corner.
可能性は満ちるストーリー 配信に夢中
Possibility-filled story, hooked on streaming.
いつかみんなで行こうよ キラララ ステラ
Let's all go someday, Kira-ra-ra Stella.
セラヴィ PRP 楽しみたい日々
C'est la vie, PRP, days we want to enjoy.
ロゴがネームに込めた四人は
The four whom the logo put in their names.
私たちは歌える きっと 5MC
We can sing, surely, 5MC!
スマホの充電足りてる？ いぇーい！BBー！もっと熱くいこう！リミット解除！おらおらで行くぞ！
Is your phone battery charged enough? Yeah! BB-! Let's get hotter! Limit released! Let's go, let's go!
stay by my side 夜中になってもまだ寝れない
stay by my side, even in the middle of the night, I still can't sleep.
イェイ あとどのくらい？辿り着くあの夢の世界
Yeah, how much longer? Reaching that dream world.
初めて会ったあの日 輪になって遊んだり
That day we met for the first time, playing in a circle...
ここまで歩いてきた未来 今でも覚えてる
The future we walked to get here, I still remember it even now.
上がるペース 夜も眠れず
Rising pace, unable to sleep at night.
置き去りにした生活リズム 12ヶ月
The daily rhythm left behind for 12 months.
進んだ道を振り返る
Looking back at the path we advanced.
普通に戻ったりしたっていいんじゃない？
Isn't it fine to return to normal?
威風堂々 今日ももう一人で抱え込まないで
With imposing grace, today too, don't hold it all alone anymore.
ほら 水くさい最後に
Look, at the reserved end...
自分らしくいる心配ない
No need to worry about being yourself.
美味しいもん食べてまた次行こう
Eat something delicious and let's go next!
になってもオーバーフローしてる
...even when we're old, we're overflowing!
Stay by my side
街角で二人
On the street corner, the two of us
By my side
考えてる一人
Thinking all alone
無駄にはならないからあの涙も
Because even those tears won't be in vain
いまここ by my side
Right here, by my side
寄り添ってる隣
Snuggled up close next to you
はい！ということで
All right! And with that...
後半ノンストップで駆け抜けてきましたが
...we ran through the second half non-stop!
ご覧の通り、衣装チェンジしてまーす！
As you can see, we've changed our outfits!
イェーイ！
Yay!
いや本当に、一人一人個性がめちゃくちゃ主張されていて素敵！
Wow, seriously, everyone's individuality really stands out, it's wonderful!
にこちゃんは、かっこいいし
Niko-chan is so cool...
ちはちゃんは、もうかっこエモいし
...Chiha-chan is so cool and emotional...
すうちゃんはもう、可愛すぎるし！
...and Suu-chan is just way too cute!
ね、それに何たって
Right? And above all...
びびちゃん、可愛いね
...Vivi-chan is so cute.
なんやその言い方！
What's with that way of saying it!
ありがとう！すうちゃんも可愛い！にこちゃんも！
Thank you! Suu-chan is cute too! Niko-chan too!
みんなに言ってる！みんなに言ってる！
She says that to everyone! She says that to everyone!
そして、ここで嬉しいお知らせがあります！
And, we have some happy news here!
なんと、このFLOW GLOWの3Dお披露目ライブが...
Incredibly, this FLOW GLOW 3D Showcase Live...
なんと！Xのトレンドで1位に！
...has reached number 1 on X's trending list!
やったー！
We did it!
オイ！オイ！オイ！
Oi! Oi! Oi!
その動き何？ちょっとテンションおかしなってる！
What is that dance? We're getting a bit too hyper!
嬉しすぎて...すいません、嬉しくて！
We're just so happy... sorry, we're just so excited!
さてさて、じゃあここまでを振り返っていきたいと思います！
Now then, let's look back on the show so far!
まずは私、吏衣那が『ダリア』と『アププンブンプン』のメドレーを披露させていただきました！
First, I, Reena, performed a medley of "Dahlia" and "Apupun Bunbun"!
『いただきました』じゃないですよ！
Don't just say "performed" like it was nothing!
もっとオブラートに包んで！
Sugarcoat it a bit more!
エロさ出てたよ！
You were being so sexy!
ジャズダンスとね、バレエ、ガールズを披露させていただきました。セクシーだったかな？
I showcased jazz dance, ballet, and girls' hip-hop. Was I sexy?
セクシーだったよ！吏衣那！
You were so sexy, Reena!
続いては？
Next up?
はい！千早が、トロンボーンとギターを自分で弾きまして、ギターの弾き語りで...
Yes! I, Chiha, played the trombone and guitar myself, and with a guitar-vocal performance...
『欲望に満ちた青年団』を歌わせていただきました！
...I sang "Yokubou ni Michita Seinendan"!
頑張った！泣いちゃったよ、千早！
You did great! I cried, Chiha!
練習してきたのでみんなに披露できて嬉しいです！聴いてくれてありがとう！
I'm so glad I could perform it for everyone after practicing so much! Thank you for listening!
そして？
And then?
はい！そして、ヴィヴィはですね、メイクを活かした『カガミ』という楽曲を歌わせていただきました！
Yes! Next, Vivi performed a song called "Kagami," making use of her makeup theme!
メイクの変化、見てくれましたか？
Did you notice the makeup changes?
あ、お尻見たの？お尻？
Ah, did you look at my butt? Your butt?
やめて！はい、そして次は？
Stop it! Okay, and next?
はい！にこは、大好きなBUMP OF CHICKENさんの『青の朔日』を、実は...
Yes! I, Niko, actually performed my favorite song "Ao no Tsuitachi" by BUMP OF CHICKEN...
ギター弾き語りです！実弾き語りです！
...with actual guitar strumming! It was a real live performance!
弾き語りと演奏をさせていただきました！めっちゃ緊張した！
I sang and played the guitar! I was so nervous!
にこのね、色んな想いを込めて歌わせていただいたので、アーカイブとか何度も見てもらえたら嬉しいです！
I poured all my feelings into singing it, so I'd be happy if you watched the archives over and over!
そしてお次は？
And who's next?
はい！すうが、『新人類』と『ギャル』のメドレーを躍らせていただきました！
Yes! I, Suu, performed a dance medley of "Shinjinrui" and "Gal"!
結構ね、かっこよく踊ったんじゃないかと思います！
I think I danced pretty cool!
かっこよかった！
You were so cool!
3メートル離れて！
Keep 3 meters away!
3メートル？ソーシャルディスタンス！
3 meters? Social distance!
はい、みんなでね、ソロを楽しんでもらった後は、私たちの新曲、そしてライブのタイトルにもなっております『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』を初披露させていただきました！
Yes! After everyone enjoyed our solo stages, we gave the first performance of our new song and the title of this live, "MAKE IT, BREAK IT"!
やったー！最高！
Yeah! The best!
今日リリース...あ、これ言っちゃダメだ！ハハハハ...
Released today... Ah, I shouldn't say that! Hahaha...
そのあとは、私たちのこの間出させていただいたシングル『stay by my side』を披露させていただきました！
After that, we performed our recently released single, "stay by my side"!
そして、ここで配信を見てくれているみんなにお知らせがあります！
And here, we have an announcement for everyone watching the stream!
なになに？
What is it? What is it?
お知らせは私たちと同じ5つあるので、一人一人紹介させていただきたいと思います！トップバッターはヴィヴィ、よろしく！
Since we have 5 announcements, just like there are 5 of us, we'll introduce them one by one! First up is Vivi, take it away!
はーい！それではこちらをご覧ください、どうぞ！
Yay! Alright, please take a look at this, go ahead!
[画面：FLOW GLOW 1st ALBUM 'EL8W' 2026.01.21 RELEASE!]
en: [On-screen: FLOW GLOW 1st ALBUM 'EL8W' 2026.01.21 RELEASE!]
[On-screen: FLOW GLOW 1st ALBUM 'EL8W' 2026.01.21 RELEASE!]
1stアルバム『EL8W』についてです！発売日は、来年1月21日！デビュー曲『FG ROADSTER』のほか、気鋭のサウンドクリエイター陣が手掛ける全9曲を収録しています！
It's about our 1st Album, "EL8W"! The release date is January 21st next year! In addition to our debut song "FG ROADSTER", it contains a total of 9 tracks produced by up-and-coming sound creators!
すごい！おめでとう！
Amazing! Congratulations!
通常盤はAタイプ、Bタイプあり、公式EC盤と全国流通盤では特典内容も違います！
The standard edition has Type-A and Type-B, and the bonus content differs between the official EC store edition and the national retail edition!
まあ皆さん、この際どちらもゲットしちゃってください！
So everyone, please take this opportunity to get both of them!
お願いします！
Please do!
そして！冒頭にも言った重大発表は、こちら！
And! The major announcement we mentioned at the beginning is this!
アルバムのリード曲になっている『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』について、続報があります！
We have follow-up news about the album's lead track, "MAKE IT, BREAK IT"!
先ほど披露した、6thシングル『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』のデジタルリリースが決定しました！
A digital release has been confirmed for our 6th single, "MAKE IT, BREAK IT," which we just performed!
やったー！デジタルリリース！
Yay! Digital release!
デジタルリリースは明日、11月24日です！みんな絶対チェックしてね！
The digital release is tomorrow, November 24th! Everyone, make sure to check it out!
そして、この『MAKE IT, BREAK IT』のMVの公開なんですが...
Also, regarding the release of the MV for "MAKE IT, BREAK IT"...
普段やったら楽曲のリリースとほぼ同時に公開やねんけど...
Normally, it would be released almost at the same time as the song...
運営さんがですね、『もっともっといいものにしたい』ということで、公開を延期することになりました！
But the staff wanted to make it even better, so the release has been postponed!
えー！でも楽しみ！
Oh! But we're looking forward to it!
その代わりね、そちらのMVには、3Dになった...
Instead, that MV will feature us in 3D...
私たちが登場します！
We're making our appearance!
さあ、皆さん、どんな内容に仕上がっているか
Now, everyone, what kind of content we've prepared...
今からめっちゃ楽しみにしててな！
please look forward to it!
かっこよく踊ったもんね
We danced so coolly, didn't we?
そう、ダンスとかもね、やりましたよ
Yeah, we did some dancing too!
はい、続いては千速、お願いします！
Alright, next up, Chihaya, please!
はーい！それではこちらをご覧ください。どうぞ！
Okay! Then please take a look at this. Go ahead!
ホロカについてです！
It's about Holo-Card!
一昨日発売された千速とニコのスタートデッキ
The Chihaya and Niko starter decks released the day before yesterday...
実は、今日のライブでお披露目した新衣装のセカンドカードが収録されているんです！
actually contain the second cards featuring the new outfits shown off in today's live!
みんなにはね、サプライズのつもりで先行してセカンド衣装入れてもらったんですが、敷、
We had them put the second outfits in early as a surprise for everyone...
びっくりしましたか？
Were you surprised?
バレちゃったね
It got found out, didn't it?
ね、実はね、出てたんだよね
Yeah, it was actually already out!
これら2つのスタートデッキは、取り扱いのあるカードショップにて販売中です。
These two starter decks are currently on sale at card shops carrying them.
気になった方はぜひ手に取ってみてください。
If you're interested, please be sure to pick them up!
ホロカに関する情報はまだまだあります！こちらもご覧ください。どうぞ！
There's still more Holo-Card news! Take a look at this too. Go ahead!
来月19日発売の新ブースターパック「アヤカシバーミリオン」
The new booster pack 'Ayakashi Vermilion' releasing next month on the 19th...
その中に、今日りっちゃんがお披露目した新衣装のセカンドが収録されています！
contains the second card featuring the new outfit Ricchan showed off today!
え、嘘、マジ！？
Wait, seriously?!
何だそれ！？何だそれ！？
What is that?! What is that?!
えー、ちょっといいな、スタッフさん、ビビとすーちゃんのも早くお願いしますよ！
Aw, I'm jealous! Staff, please hurry up with Vivy's and Su-chan's too!
お願い〜！お願いします！
Please! We're begging you!
楽しみだね
We can't wait!
はい、では続いては、すーちゃんお願いします！
Alright, next up, Su-chan, please!
はーい！
Yeees!
ホロライブ公式ぬいぐるみブランド、ホロライブ・フレンズ・ウィズ・ユー、通称ホロフレ！
Hololive's official plushie brand, "hololive friends with u"—commonly known as Holo-Fre...
ついに私たち、FLOW GLOWの5人が登場します！
is finally releasing plushies for the five of us in FLOW GLOW!
やったー！ついにだ！
Yay! Finally!
今年のエキスポで開発決定とお知らせしてから、やっと皆さんにお届けできるようになりました！
Since we announced their development at this year's Expo, we can finally deliver them to you!
注目は髪型や衣装、とにかく再現度がすごい！
Check out the hair and outfits—the attention to detail is amazing!
今日の22時より予約開始となりますので、お見逃しなく！
Reservations start tonight at 22:00, so don't miss out!
続いてのグッズがこちら！
And here's our next merchandise!
今回お披露目した3Dの姿が、アクリルスタンドになります！
The 3D forms we showed off today are becoming acrylic stands!
先輩たちの3Dアクスタを持ってる人なら分かると思うんですが、
If you own any of our seniors' 3D acrylic stands, you probably know...
かなり大きめのサイズとなっております！
they are actually quite large in size!
存在感ばっちりな私たちの3Dアクスタ、ぜひ手にとってください！
Our 3D acrylic stands have a great presence, so please be sure to get them!
こちらもホロフレと同じ、今日の22時より予約開始となりますので、合わせてチェックしてくれると嬉しいです！
Reservations start tonight at 22:00, just like the plushies, so please check them out together!
続いては、ニコ、お願いします！
Next up, Niko, please!
はーい！
Yeees!
まずは、こちらをご覧ください。どうぞ！
First, take a look at this. Go ahead!
池袋にある、じゃなくて、
In Ikebukuro... wait, no,
池袋にあるタワーレコード渋谷、サンシャインシティアルパ店ほか、全国のタワーレコード12店舗！そこで！
Tower Records Shibuya, Sunshine City Alpa in Ikebukuro, and 12 other Tower Records stores nationwide! There...
FLOW GLOWファーストアルバム発売を記念したポップアップの開催が決定！
we are holding a pop-up shop to celebrate the release of FLOW GLOW's 1st album!
やったー！
Yay!
今まで公式オンラインでしか手に入らなかったミックステープの1、2のほか、
In addition to Mixtapes 1 and 2, which were online-exclusive...
先ほど紹介したFGのホロフレ、グッズも盛りだくさんとなっております！
we'll also have the Holo-Fre plushies and tons of other merch!
またですね、期間中にグッズをお買い上げの方にはノベルティももらえる予定となっておりますので、
Also, customers who purchase merchandise during the event will receive a special novelty gift!
期間は1月20日から2月8日まで！
The event runs from January 20th to February 8th!
グッズに関する詳しい情報やノベルティ条件などについては、
For details on the merchandise and novelty conditions...
12月中旬開設予定の特設ページをご覧ください！
please check the special site scheduled to open in mid-December!
最後はリオナ、お願いします！
Lastly, Riona, please!
はーーい！
Yeees!
それではこちらをご覧ください。どうぞ！
Then please take a look at this. Go ahead!
このあと、FLOW GLOW公式チャンネルのメンバーシップにて、アフタートークライブがあります！
After this, we'll have an after-talk stream on our official membership channel!
そっちにも足を運びたいなというそこのあなた、
To those of you who want to come over and watch...
ぜひ今のうちにメンバーシップの登録をお願いします！
please join our membership ahead of time!
そのアフタートークライブは、ここでは無く別のステージからお届けします。
This after-talk stream will be broadcast from a different stage.
そこだけでしか聞けないライブの裏話とか、あとはファーストアルバムに収録されている曲の中から、
With behind-the-scenes live stories you can only hear there, plus...
あの曲を披露したいと思います！
we will perform THAT song from our first album!
どう？ますます気になってきたんじゃない？
What do you think? Aren't you getting curious?
気になる！待ってるからね！
I'm curious! We'll be waiting!
また、私たち一人一人のチャンネルのメンバーシップでも、推しカメラ配信もあります！
Also, each of our individual member channels will have focus-camera streams!
ぜひそっちものぞきに来てね！
So please come check those out too!
そして、12月9日からの定期配信は3Dとなります！
And our regular streams starting December 9th will be in 3D!
やったー！お楽しみに！
Yay! Look forward to it!
さて、皆さん、楽しい時間はあっという間ですが...
Now, everyone, fun times fly by so quickly...
そろそろライブも終了となります。
and it's almost time for this live to end.
嫌だー！
Nooo!
せっかくなので、ステージの思い出を写真に撮りたいんですけど、
Since we're here, we'd like to take a photo to remember the stage...
撮ろう撮ろう！みんな並んで
Let's take one! Everyone, line up!
いい感じ？写ってる？写ってるよ
Is it good? Are we in frame? We're in!
じゃあ行くよ、はい、チーズ！
Okay, here we go! Say cheese!
パシャパシャパシャ！撮れたかな？
Click, click, click! Did everyone get it?
よし、ありがとう！すーちゃんよくやったね
Alright, thank you! Good job, Su-chan!
すーちゃんのおかげで素敵な思い出も撮れたところで、
Now that we've captured a wonderful memory thanks to Su-chan...
ここでメンバー一人一人から、ファンのみなさんにメッセージをお届けしたいと思います。
we'd like to deliver a message to all our fans from each of us.
まずはすーちゃんから！
First up, Su-chan!
はい！FLOW GLOW、そしてFLOWME、ここまで一緒に走ってきてくれてありがとうございます！
Yes! FLOW GLOW and FLOWME, thank you so much for running with us this far!
みんなのおかげで3Dになれたよー！
Thanks to everyone, we were able to debut in 3D!
ここから先も色んな思い出をみんなと一緒に作っていきたいです。
I want to continue making many more memories together with everyone.
よろしくお願いします！
Please keep supporting us!
りー！ はい！
Rii! Yes!
いつも応援してくださるフローミーの皆さん
To all the Flow-mi who always support us,
そして、メンバー、みんな、いつもありがとう！
and to the members, everyone, thank you always!
みんながいるからここまでこれました
Because of everyone, we've made it this far.
2周年目もみんなと一緒に、どんどん花道登っていきましょう！
Let's keep climbing the flowery path together in our second year!
これからもよろしくね！ほんまにありがとう！
Please keep supporting us! Thank you so much!
さあ、続きまして、にこはどうですか？
Now, next up, Niko, how about you?
FG... はい
FG... Yes?
出会ってくれてありがとう。
Thank you for meeting me.
ありがとう。 あ、こちらこそありがとう。
Thank you. Oh, likewise, thank you.
フローグロウというダイヤモンドに気づけたあなた、天才じゃん！
To have noticed the diamond that is Flow Glow... you're a genius!
これからもよろしく、フローミー。ありがとう！
Keep supporting us, Flow-mi. Thank you!
イェーイ！ ちよは？
Yay! Chiyo?
あ、はい、ちよでございます。
Ah, yes, this is Chiyo.
いや、本当にね、今日という日をこの5人で迎えられたことが本当に嬉しく思いますし、
I'm really glad we could welcome this day as these five,
このたくさんの方に我々のね、3Dのお披露目を見守っていただけたことも本当に嬉しく思います。最後まで見ていただいてありがとうございました。
and I'm so happy so many people watched our 3D debut. Thank you for watching until the end.
ここからね、我々5人がもっともっと未来に向かって突き進んでいく姿、絶対に
From here on, the sight of the five of us pushing forward into the future...
見逃さないでくださいね！今日は本当にありがとう！
please don't miss it! Thank you so much for today!
免許も待ってます！ 待ってるよー！
I'm waiting for your driver's license too! We're waiting!
はい、最後、りっちゃん！
Alright, last is Ricchan!
はい！デビュー当初からずっと夢だった、歌って踊る姿を届ける...届けることが本当に嬉しく思います！
Yes! I'm so happy to show you my singing and dancing, which has been my dream since debut!
ここまで応援してくださって、本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for supporting us up to this point!
そしてね、私たちはこれからも... ちょっとおいでよ。ちょっとおいでよ、みんな。
And you know, from now on, we... Come here a sec. Everyone, come here a sec.
お、いいとこ、いいとこ！ みんないいとこ！
Oh, perfect timing! Everyone, close in!
リーダー、みたらし団子みたいになってるからやめて！
Leader, you look like a mitarashi dango, stop that!
あー！リーダーが押しつぶされちゃう！
Ah! The leader is getting crushed!
喋ってるじゃん！
I'm trying to talk here!
ちょっと男子！
Hey, boys!
あ、まだ？ごめんね！
Ah, not yet? Sorry!
あのね、これからもね、私たち一人一人の歩みをね、みんなにね、見守ってほしいな！
You see, from now on, I want everyone to keep watching over our individual paths!
だから、フローグロウのこと、みんなこれからもよろしくね！
So, please continue to support Flow Glow!
はい、どうぞ！アンコール！
Now, please! Encore!
ちょっと、違う、違う！
Wait, that's not it, that's not it!
バレてる、バレてる。
They've figured it out, they know!
ここじゃないか？ちょっと早かったかな？
Is it not here? Was it a bit too early?
うん、早かった。
Yeah, too early.
どうする？お別れする？これで終わりなの？
What should we do? Say goodbye? Is this the end?
バイバイしよう。最後に挨拶する？
Let's say goodbye. Shall we do our final greeting?
そうだね、挨拶しよう。
Yeah, let's do our greeting.
それでは、私たち、せーの！フローグロウでした！
And so, we are... One, two... Flow Glow!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ばいばいよ、んー、ちゅ！
Bye-bye! Mwah!
うーん、びびー！大好きやで！ちゅっ！
Beep beep! I love you! Chu!
本当にありがとう。んー、ちゅっ。
Thank you so much. Mwah.
ありがとう、んー、まっ！
Thank you, mwah!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
FG ROADSTER
フローミー、アンコールありがとう！
Flow-mi, thank you for the encore!
今日は最高のライブでした！
Today was the best live show ever!
みんな楽しんでくれたかな？
Did everyone have fun?
最後はやっぱりこの曲！
For the last, it has to be this song!
FGロードスター！
FG Roadster!
搭載 V8 エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第7感 持ってる 原人
A hominid with a seventh sense
狂う この 世界 と 全 人類
This crazy world and all humanity
この 5人 で ゲーム を チェンジ
The five of us will change the game
唸る 4輪 発射 セヨ
Launch the four roaring wheels!
皆さん 3キュー サランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, saranghaeyo!
操る 2台 の turntable
Spinning two turntables
獲る 1番 ここ ground 0
Aiming for number one here at Ground Zero
リスク 超え て 挑戦
Take on the challenge beyond risk
1000キャストもセットだ 1000
A thousand, and the cast is also set, a thousand
上りあげる頂点
Climbing to the very top
座布団つんでクッション
Piling up cushions for comfort
舞い込むエグゼクティブ ロードスタート
The executives fly in, Roadster start!
特殊部隊 集合 能力者
Special forces assemble, ability users!
この歴史に名を残す 超豪華
Leaving our names in history, super luxurious!
ぶっちぎりで置き去り 加速中
Leaving everyone behind, accelerating far ahead!
今 高速でブチ抜いていく 大気圏
Now, breaking through the atmosphere at high speed,
エンジンからジェットの鼓動 揺れている 対流圏
the jet heartbeat from the engine shakes the troposphere.
眼下に広がる大地 超えていく地球儀線
Over the land spreading below, crossing the lines of the globe.
バックミラーにビッグブルー 映ってる I-P-F-Y-A
The big blue is reflected in the rearview mirror, I-P-F-Y-A!
打ち上げたいから飛んでく
Since we want to launch it, we fly out,
打ち鳴らせたいこの燃料
wanting to ignite this fuel.
打ち砕けないアステロイドが群がれる 寿司食べたい
Unbreakable asteroids swarm around, "I want to eat sushi!"
見上げる世界ビジョン
Looking up at the world vision,
燃えてるメンバー一同
all the members are on fire.
他愛もない 臥薪嘗胆 新光景 超えていく 世界規模
With no trivial hardships, a new scene, going beyond on a global scale!
奏でるはずだモンスター
It's bound to play, the Monster!
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are Monsters!
エリアじゃ足りない
This area isn't enough,
FGパーティハイ
FG party high!
光るテールはスター
The glowing tail lights are stars,
ヘヴィブースター 目覚めていく本能
heavy booster, awakening our instinct,
蒼い炎
blue flames.
BFF Let's go out
すり抜けながら ゼロから
Slipping through, starting from zero,
空まで囚われ
capturing all the way to the sky.
走るFGロードスター
The running FG Roadster,
唸るブースター
the roaring booster.
ROAD ROAD STAGE 3
今 チェイスミー
Now, Chase me!
ターボ付きスーパーカー
A super car equipped with a turbo,
ハンドルさばく教習所
handling the wheel at the driving school.
複座式 助手席 超ばっか
Double-seater, the passenger seat is filled with the best,
次元が違うレベチばっか
they are all on a completely different level.
コーナー攻めるギリギリ
Attacking the corners to the absolute limit,
モーター全開ビリビリ
motor at full throttle, electric sensation!
ソーラーカラーみちびき
Guided by solar colors,
お肌がピチピチ
with youthful, glowing skin!
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツターン
Burning the tires with a donut turn,
弾け飛んでいくドラム缶
drum cans sending flying away.
顧客満足度高くて ぶち上げる お客さん
High customer satisfaction, hyping up the audience!
ゼロから最高到達点
From zero to the highest peak,
照りつける太陽光発電
shining bright like solar power generation.
達するこの小惑星 超覚醒 突入 ボーナスステージ
Reaching this asteroid, super awakening, entering the bonus stage!
一直線伸びているロード
A road extending in a straight line,
バイブレーション エンジンの鼓動
vibration, the heartbeat of the engine.
速度増し上がっている駆動
The drive is picking up speed,
限界重力 凌駕し上昇
surpassing the limit of gravity and rising up.
開拓しまくっていくフロンティア
Continuing to pioneer the frontier,
旅立つロードスター オンリーワン
the roadster sets off, the only one.
アクセル踏み込んでいくドンピシャ
Stepping on the pedal, perfectly on target,
飛んでく日本一さ
flying to be number one in Japan!
1億馬力の超低音
The super bass of a hundred million horsepower,
火星のホテルが休憩所
the hotel on Mars is our rest area.
並んで走行 UFO
Running side by side with a UFO,
降り立つ宇宙ステーション
landing on the space station.
物語の継承
Inheritance of the story,
まるで旧約聖書
just like the Old Testament.
この先何世紀も成長
Growing for centuries to come,
生き延びていくテイクオフ
surviving through the takeoff.
奏でるはずだモンスター
It's bound to play, the Monster!
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are Monsters!
エリアじゃ足りない
This area isn't enough,
FGパーティハイ
FG party high!
光るテールはスター
The glowing tail lights are stars,
ヘヴィブースター 目覚めていく本能
heavy booster, awakening our instinct,
蒼い炎
blue flames.
BFF Let's go out
すり抜けながら ゼロから
Slipping through, starting from zero,
空まで囚われ
capturing all the way to the sky.
走るFGロードスター
The running FG Roadster,
唸るブースター
the roaring booster.
ROAD ROAD STAGE 3
今 チェイスミー
Now, Chase me!
以上 私たち
That's all from us,
FLOW GLOW でした！
we were FLOW GLOW!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
FLOW GLOW 3D LIVE / みんな本当にありがとう！
[FLOW GLOW 3D LIVE / Thank you so much, everyone!]
you'll see !
You'll see!